Guide to the Pirie MacDonald Portrait Photographs [1885]-1942 (bulk 1900-1942) PR 39
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Portrait Photographs
  - Baden-Powell, Robert Stephenson Smyth (1857-1941), military officer, 1919 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bainbridge, William Seaman (1870-1947), surgeon; military officer, 1934 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bairnsfather, Captain Bruce (1888-1959), illustrator, 1918 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 13)
  - Baker, George Pierce (1866-1935), educator, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 14)
  - Baker, Ray Stannard ["David Grayson"] (1870-1940), author, 1937 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ballin, Hugo (1879-1956), painter, 1931 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 16)
  - Barber, Samuel (1910-1981), composer, 1940 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 17)
  - Barry, Philip (1896-1949), playwright, 1922 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bartlett, Paul Wayland (1865-1925), sculptor, 1915 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 19)
  - Barton, Bruce (1886-1967), advertising executive, author, politician, 1924 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 20)
  - Baruch, Bernard Mannes (1870-1965), economist, financier, statesman, 1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 21)
  - Battle, George Gordon (1868-1949), lawyer, 1909 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 22)
  - Beach, Chester (1881-1956), sculptor, 1931 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 23)
  - Beard, Daniel Carter (1850-1941), artist, author, editor, 1920 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 24)
  - Beckwith, Edmund Ruffin (1890-1949), lawyer, 1939 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bedaux, Charles E. (1886-1944), industrial engineer, 1932 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 26)
  - Bedford, Edward Thomas (1849-1931), businessman, 1909 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bedford, Frederick Thomas (1877-1963), businessman, 1932 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 28)
  - Beers, Clifford Whittingham (1876-1943), founder of the Mental Hygiene movement, 1932 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 29)
  - Beith, John Hay ["Ian Hay"] (1876-1952), novelist, playwright, military officer, 1916 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 30)
  - Benedict, Elias Cornelius (1834-1920), banker, 1903 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 31)
  - Benet, Stephen Vincent (1898-1943), poet, author, 1935 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 32)
  - Benet, William Rose (1886-1950), author, 1934 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 33)
  - Benjamin, Park (1849-1922), author, patent lawyer, editor, 1902 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931), novelist, 1911 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 35)
  - Beveridge, Albert Jeremiah (1862-1927), politician, 1914 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 36)
  - Black, Frank Swett (1853-1913), politician, 1904 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 37)
  - Blashfield, Edwin Howland (1848-1936), painter, 1915 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bloom, Sol (1870-1945), politician, 1928 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 39)
  - Blythe, Samuel George (1868-1947), author, 1913 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bok, William Edward (1863-1930), editor, 1909 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bolton, Guy Reginald (1881-1979), playwright, 1924 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 42)
  - Borglum, Solon Hannibal (1868-1922), sculptor, 1906 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 43)
  - Boyd, Ernest Augustus (1887-1946), author, critic, 1925 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 44)
  - Boyd, James (1888-1944), author, 1925 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 45)
  - Brady, Anthony Nicholas (1843-1913), capitalist, 1906 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 46)
  - Brady, Nicholas Frederic (1878-1930), capitalist, 1907 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 47)
  - Brenner, Victor David (1871-1924), medallist, sculptor, 1913 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 48)
  - Bridges, Robert ["Droch"] (1858-1941), editor, author, 1931 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 49)
  - Brisbane, Arthur (1864-1936), editor, 1906 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 50)
  - Brockway, Howard (1870-1951), composer, 1931 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 51)
  - Brooks, Van Wyck (1886-1963), author, critic, 1926 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 52)
  - Broun, Heywood (1888-1939), journalist, playwright, 1908 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 53)
  - Brown, Elmer Ellsworth (1861-1934), educator, 1926 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 54)
  - Browne, Lewis (1897-1949), author, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 55)
  - Brownell, William Crary (1851-1928), editor, author, 1915 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 56)
  - Brush, George DeForest (1855-1941), artist, 1917 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 57)
  - Bunau-Varilla, Philippe (1859-1940), French statesman, 1903 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 58)
  - Burgess, Frank Gelett (1886-1951), author, 1924 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 59)
  - Burroughs, John (1837-1921), naturalist, author, 1906 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 60)
  - Burton, Richard Eugene (1861-1940), poet, educator, 1931 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 61)
  - Bush, Irving T. (1869-1948), businessman, 1918 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 62)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray (1862-1947), university president, 1915 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 63)
  - Cable, George Washington (1844-1925), author, 1915 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 64)
  - Cadman, Samuel Parkes (1864-1936), clergyman, 1909 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 65)
  - Calder, A. Stirling (1870-1945), sculptor, 1931 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 66)
  - Canby, Henry Seidel (b. 1878), editor, 1933 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 67)
  - Cardozo, Benjamin Nathan (1870-1938), jurist - [three-quarter pose], 1914 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cardozo, Benjamin Nathan (1870-1938), jurist - [three-quarter pose, without glasses], 1927 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 69)
  - Carman, Bliss (1861-1929), poet, 1903 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 70)
  - Carnegie, Dale (1888-1955), author, lecturer, 1928 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 71)
  - Carpenter, John Alden (1876-1951), composer, 1932 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 72)
  - Carrel, Alexis (1873-1944), surgeon, biologist, 1939 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 73)
  - Carty, John J. (1861-1932), electrical engineer, 1925 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 74)
  - Chaffee, Adna Romanza (1842-1914), military officer, 1905 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 75)
  - Chanler, Lewis Stuyvesant (1869-1942), lawyer, 1908 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 76)
  - Channing, Edward (1856-1931), educator, historian, 1926 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 77)
  - Chapin, Roy Dikeman (1880-1936), industrialist, 1921 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 78)
  - Chapman, John J. (1862-1933), author, 1908 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 79)
  - Chapple, Joseph Mitchell (1867-1950), editor, author, 1923 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 80)
  - Chase, Stuart (1888-1985), author, economist, 1932 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 81)
  - Chatfield-Taylor, Hobart C. (1865-1945), author, 1934 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 82)
  - Christian X (1870-1947), Danish King, 1921 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 83)
  - Chrysler, Walter, Jr. (1909-1988), capitalist, philanthropist, 1938 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 84)
  - Clarke, Gilmore David (1892-1938), engineer, landscape architect, educator, 1937 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 85)
  - Clews, Henry (1840-1923), banker, 1902 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 86)
  - Cobb, Irvin Shrewsbury (1876-1944), author, 1912 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 87)
  - Cockran, William Bourke (1854-1923), politician, 1913 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 88)
  - Cole, Timothy (1852-1931), wood engraver, 1915 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 89)
  - Collier, Robert Joseph (1876-1918), editor, publisher, 1916 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 90)
  - Comstock, Cyrus. A., merchant, 1936 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 91)
  - Connelly, Marc (1890-1980), playwright, 1923 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 92)
  - Copeland, Charles Townsend (1860-1952), educator, 1915 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 93)
  - Cosgrave, William Thomas (1880-1965), Irish statesman, 1928 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 94)
  - Coudert, Frederic R., Sr. (1871-1955), lawyer, 1913 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 95)
  - Cox, Kenyon (1856-1919), painter, 1906 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 96)
  - Coykendall, Frederick (1872-1954), shipping executive. publisher, 1935 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 97)
  - Cram, Ralph Adams (1863-1942), architect, author, critic, 1936 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 98)
  - Crawford, Francis Marion (1854-1909), novelist, historian, 1903 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 99)
  - Cromwell, William Nelson (1854-1948), lawyer, 1939; See also: Box 19, folder 440 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 100)
  - Crooks, Richard Alexander (1910-1972), tenor, 1933 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 101)
  - Cross, Wilbur Lucius (1862-1948), educator, author, editor, politician, 1923 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 102)
  - Dabo, Leon (1868-1960), artist, 1921 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 103)
  - Damrosch, Frank Heino (1859-1937), musician, musical director, 1913 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 104)
  - Damrosch, Walter Johannes (1862-1950), conductor, composer [profile pose, black jacket], 1919 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 105)
  - Damrosch, Walter Johannes (1862-1950), conductor, composer [profile pose, gray jacket], 1936; See also: Box 19, folder 443 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 106)
  - Davenport, Homer Calvin (1867-1912), illustrator, 1903 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 107)
  - Davis, Norman H. (1878-1944), financier, 1923 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 108)
  - Davis, Richard Harding (1864-1916), novelist, 1915 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 109)
  - Davis, Vernon Mansfield (1855-1931), jurist, 1908 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 110)
  - Davison, Henry Pomeroy (1867-1922), banker, 1909 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 111)
  - Dawson, Coningsby William (1883-1959), author, 1920 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 112)
  - Day, Joseph P. (b. 1873), real estate auctioneer, 1922 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 113)
  - Delano, William Adams (1874-1960), architect, 1936 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 114)
  - Derby, Richard (1881-1963), surgeon, 1917 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 115)
  - Dewey, Charles Melville (1849-1937), painter, 1913 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 116)
  - Dielman, Frederick (1847-1935), painter, 1931 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 117)
  - Doherty, Henry Latham (1870-1939), public utilities executive, 1908 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 118)
  - Doran, George Henry (1869-1956), author, editor, publisher, 1924 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 119)
  - Dos Passos, John Randolph (1844-1917), lawyer, 1907 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 120)
  - Doyle, Arthur Conan (1859-1930), English author, 1922 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 121)
  - Dreiser, Theodore (1871-1945), novelist, 1907 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 122)
  - Drinkwater, John (1882-1937), poet, dramatist, 1925 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 123)
  - Dumond, Frank Vincent (1865-1951), artist, instructor, 1936 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 124)
  - Durant, William James (1885-1981), author, educator, 1927 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 125)
  - Duveen, Joseph (1869-1939), art dealer, art patron, 1915 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 126)
  - Eaton, Charles Warren (1857-1937), painter, 1908 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 127)
  - Eaton, Walter Prichard (1878-1957), author, educator, critic, 1931 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 128)
  - Edman, Irwin (1896-1954), educator, author, 1940 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 129)
  - Edwards, George Wharton (1869-1950), painter, illustrator, 1931 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 130)
  - Egan, Maurice Francis (1852-1924), diplomat, editor, author, 1921 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 131)
  - Erdmann, John Frederic (1864-1954), surgeon, 1938 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 132)
  - Erskine, John (1879-1951), novelist, essayist, musician, 1936 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 133)
  - Ervine, St. John Greer (1883-1971), Irish dramatist, novelist, 1928 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 134)
  - Fargo, James Congdel (1829-1915), financier, 1901 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 135)
  - Farrar, John C. (1896-1974), editor, author, 1921 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 136)
  - Farrow, Miles (1871-1953), organist, composer, 1926 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 137)
  - Field, Marshall (1835-1906), merchant, philanthropist, 1903 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 138)
  - Field, Marshall III (1893-1956), corporation director, publisher, 1935 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 139)
  - Finley, John Huston (1863-1940) editor [three-quarter pose, tilted head], 1903 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 140)
  - Finley, John Huston (1863-1940) editor [three-quarter pose], 1913 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 141)
  - Firestone, Harvey Samuel, Sr. (1868-1938), industrialist, 1915 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 142)
  - Firestone, Harvey Samuel, Jr. (b. 1898), industrialist, 1930 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 143)
  - Fish, Hamilton, Sr. (1849-1936), politician, 1908 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 144)
  - Fisher, Harrison (1877-1934), artist [three-quarter pose], 1922 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 145)
  - Flanagan, John F. (1865-1952), sculptor, 1922 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 146)
  - Ford, Edsel Bryant (1893-1943), industrialist, 1934 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 147)
  - Ford, Henry (1863-1947), industrialist, 1934 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 148)
  - Ford, Simeon (1855-1933), businessman, orator, 1902 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 149)
  - Fox, Dixon Ryan (1887-1945), historian, university president, 1937 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 150)
  - French, Daniel Chester (1850-1931), sculptor, 1913 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 151)
  - French, Frederick Fillmore (1884-1936), businessman, 1924 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 152)
  - French, John Denton Pinkstone (1852-1925), English military officer, 1922 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 153)
  - Friml, Rudolf (1884-1972), composer, pianist, 1927 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 154)
  - Funk, Wilfred John (1883-1965), publisher, 1932 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 155)
  - Garland, Hamlin (1860-1940), novelist, dramatist, 1919 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 156)
  - Gary, Elbert Henry (1846-1927), jurist, industrialist, 1925 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 157)
  - Gates, John Warne (1855-1911), financier, 1908 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 158)
  - Geddes, Norman Bel (1893-1958), designer, author, producer, 1930 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 159)
  - Gibson, Charles Dana (1867-1944), painter, illustrator, 1903 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 160)
  - Gifford, Walter Sherman (1885-1966), businessman, 1925 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 161)
  - Gill, Enrique (b. 1890), Argentine lawyer, 1941 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 162)
  - Gilbert, Cass (1859-1934), architect, 1918 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 163)
  - Giles, Howard Everett (1876-1955), painter, 1914 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 164)
  - Gillette, William H. (1855-1937), actor, playwright, 1917 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 165)
  - Gilman, Lawrence (1878-1939), critic, author, editor, 1931 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 166)
  - Glackens, William J. (1870-1938), painter, 1936 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 167)
  - Gogarty, Oliver St. John (1878-1957), author, 1933 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 168)
  - Goldman, Albert (1882-1967), government official, 1939 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 169)
  - Gordon, Charles William (1860-1937), Canadian clergyman, author, 1929 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 170)
  - Goudy, Frederic William (1865-1947), type designer, 1934 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 171)
  - Grady, George (1888-1956), printer, 1939 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 172)
  - Grainger, Percy A. (1882-1961), composer, pianist, 1916 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 173)
  - Gregory, John (1879-1958), sculptor, 1931 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 174)
  - Gray, Zane (1875-1939), novelist, 1920 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 175)
  - Groll, Albert Lorey (1866-1952), painter, printmaker, 1937 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 176)
  - Hadley, Arthur Twining (1856-1930), university president, 1918 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 177)
  - Hadley, Henry K. (1871-1937), composer, 1925 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 178)
  - Haenschen, Walter Gustave (1889-1980), composer, conductor, 1931 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 179)
  - Hamilton, Clayton Meeker (1881-1946), editor, critic, playwright, 1931 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 180)
  - Hammond, John Hayes (1855-1936), mining engineer, 1902 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 181)
  - Hannay, James Owen ["George A. Birmingham"] (1865-1910), Irish clergyman, novelist, playwright, 1913 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 182)
  - Harbach, Otto Abels (1873-1963), playwright, 1925 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 183)
  - Harper, George McLean (1863-1947), educator, 1936 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 184)
  - Harriman, Oliver (1862-1940), financier, 1912 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 185)
  - Haskell, William Nafew (1878-1952), military officer, 1937 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 186)
  - Hassam, Childe (1859-1935), painter, printmaker, 1923 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 187)
  - Hayes, Carleton J. H. (1882-1964), educator, diplomat, 1931 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 188)
  - Hedges, Job Elmer (1862-1925), lawyer, 1912 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 189)
  - Held, John, Jr. (1889-1958), illustrator, 1924 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 190)
  - Herbert, Victor (1859-1924), composer, conductor, 1906 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 191)
  - Hewitt, Peter Cooper (1861-1921), scientist, inventor, 1911 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 192)
  - Higgins, Frank Wayland (1856-1907), politician, 1903 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 193)
  - Hill, Edward Burlingame (1872-1957), musician, composer, 1931 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 194)
  - Hill, George Washington (1884-1946), businessman, 1922 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 195)
  - Hogan, Frank J. (1877-1944), lawyer, bibliophile, 1938 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 196)
  - Howard, Sidney (Coe) (1891-1939), playwright, 1925 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 197)
  - Howells, John Mead (1868-1959), architect, 1931 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 198)
  - Hoyt, Colgate (1849-1922), banker, 1901 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 199)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans (1862-1948), lawyer, jurist, politician, 1904 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 200)
  - Hughes, Hatcher (1881-1945), dramatist, educator, 1936 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 201)
  - Huneker, James Gibbons (1860-1921), music critic, author, 1906 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 202)
  - Inge, William Ralph (1860-1954), English clergyman, author, lecturer, 1925 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 203)
  - Jackson, Dugald Caleb (1865-1951), electrical engineer, author, 1939 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 204)
  - James, Philip (1890-1975), composer, conductor, 1936 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 205)
  - Jennewein, Carl Paul (1890-1978), sculptor, 1933 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 206)
  - Jerome, William Travers (1859-1934), lawyer, 1905 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 207)
  - Johansen, John Christian (1876-1964), painter, 1934 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 208)
  - Johnson, Edward (1881-1959), Canadian tenor, opera manager, 1938 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 209)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood (1853-1937), editor, author, 1908 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 210)
  - Jones, Robert Edmond (1887-1954), set and graphic designer, 1922 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 211)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar Bernhard (1877-1956), author, 1917 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 212)
  - Kelley, Cornelius Francis (1875-1957), industrialist, 1908 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 213)
  - Kendall, William Mitchell (1856-1941), architect, 1931 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 214)
  - Kendall, William Sergeant (1869-1938), painter, sculptor, 1931 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 215)
  - Ketten, Maurice (b. 1875), illustrator, 1908 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 216)
  - Kingsley, Darwin Pearl (1857-1932), businessman, 1914 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 217)
  - Kinney, Troy (1871-1938), artist, author, 1931 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 218)
  - Kirby, Thomas Ellis (1846-1924), art auctioneer, 1923 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 219)
  - Kroll, Leon (1884-1974), painter, 1931 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 220)
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood (1893-1970), author, educator, 1937 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 221)
  - La Farge, Bancel (1865-1938), painter, 1936 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 222)
  - Lang, William Cosmo Gordon (1864-1945), English clergyman [half-length, seated, white robe], 1918 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 223)
  - Lawrence, William (1850-1941), clergyman [three-quarter pose], 1916 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 224)
  - Lawson, Ernest (1873-1939), painter, 1931 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 225)
  - Le Boutillier, Philip (b. 1880), merchant, 1931 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 226)
  - Lee, Ivy Ledbetter (1877-1934), publicist, 1913 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 227)
  - LeGallienne, Richard (1866-1947), author, poet, novelist, 1902 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 228)
  - Lehman, Irving (1876-1945), jurist, 1909 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 229)
  - Lippmann, Walter (1889-1974), editor, author, 1936 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 230)
  - Littleton, Martin Wiley (1872-1934), lawyer, 1916 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 231)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot (1850-1924), politician, 1915 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 232)
  - Lodge, Oliver (1851-1940), English scientist [profile pose], 1920 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 233)
  - Lorillard, Pierre (1860-1940), businessman, 1912 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 234)
  - Low, Will Hicok (1853-1932), artist, 1913 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 235)
  - Lumiere, Antoine (1846-1911), French painter, photographer, 1907 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 236)
  - Mabie, Hamilton Wright (1846-1916), editor, author, 1915 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 237)
  - McAdoo, William Gibbs (1863-1941), politician, 1903 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 238)
  - McClellan, George Brinton (1865-1940), politician, 1905 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 239)
  - McCormack, John (1884-1945), tenor, 1937 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 240)
  - McCormick, Cyrus Hall (1859-1936), businessman, 1935 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 241)
  - MacCracken, Henry Noble (1880-1970), college president, 1924 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 242)
  - McCutcheon, George Barr (1866-1928), author, 1919 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 243)
  - MacDonald, Carlos Frederick (1845-1926), psychiatrist (Offsite-box 10, Folder 244)
  - MacDonald, John (1844-1911), businessman, 1903 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 245)
  - MacDonald, Pirie (1867-1942), photographer [in Scottish regalia], 1901 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 246)
  - MacDonald, Pirie (1867-1942), photographer [in Boy Scout uniform], 1921 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 247)
  - MacDonald, Pirie (1867-1942), photographer [three-quarter pose, with glasses], 1930 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 248)
  - MacDonald, Pirie (1867-1942), photographer [in studio with camera and wall of portraits], 1933 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 249)
  - MacDonald, Pirie (1867-1942), photographer [in studio, seated and holding clipboard], 1936 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 250)
  - MacDonald, Pirie (1867-1942), photographer [three-quarter pose, without glasses], 1940 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 251)
  - McFee, William (1881-1960), author, 1933 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 252)
  - MacKaye, Percy (1875-1956), dramatist, author, 1936 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 253)
  - Mallory, Charles Henry (1892-1953), broker, 1915 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 254)
  - Malone, Dudley Field (1882-1950), lawyer, 1910 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 255)
  - Manning, William Thomas (1866-1949), clergyman, 1921 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 256)
  - Manship, Paul (1885-1966), sculptor, 1931 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 257)
  - Markham, Edwin (1852-1940), poet, lecturer, 1903 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 258)
  - Marquis, Donald Robert Perry (1878-1937), author, playwright, 1928 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 259)
  - Martin, Bradley (1841-1913), lawyer, financier, 1909 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 260)
  - Masaryk, Jan (1866-1948), Czech politician, 1919 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 261)
  - Masaryk, Thomas Garrigue (1850-1937), Czech politician, 1920 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 262)
  - Mason, Daniel Gregory (1873-1953), composer, 1938 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 263)
  - Massaguer, Conrado (1889-1965), Cuban illustrator, 1932 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 264)
  - Masters, Edgar Lee (1869-1950), author, poet, 1919 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 265)
  - Mather, Frank Jewett, Jr. (1868-1953), educator, author, 1936 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 266)
  - Matthews, Brander (1852-1929), educator, 1906 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 267)
  - Maugham, W. Somerset (1874-1965), English author, 1935 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 268)
  - Mead, D. Irving (1875-1951), banker, 1934 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 269)
  - Mead, William Rutherford (1846-1928), architect, 1918 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 270)
  - Menken, Arthur, newsreel correspondent, 1941 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 271)
  - Milford, Humphrey Sumner (1877-1952), English publisher, 1929 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 272)
  - Miller, Nathan L. (1868-1953), politician, jurist, 1940 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 273)
  - Miller, Warner (1838-1918), politician, 1906 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 274)
  - Mills, Darius Ogden (1825-1910), banker, financier, philanthropist, 1902 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 275)
  - Morley, Christopher D. (1890-1990), author, 1921 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 276)
  - Mumford, Lewis (1895-1990), author, 1936 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 277)
  - Murphy, John Francis (1853-1921), painter, 1902 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 278)
  - Nast, Thomas (1840-1902), artist, illustrator (Offsite-box 12, Folder 279)
  - Nathan, George Jean (1882-1958), author, editor, critic, 1933 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 280)
  - Nathan, Robert G. (1894-1985), author, 1936 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 281)
  - Newcombe, George (b. 1906), industrialist, 1942 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 282)